# SEDRAK ADOYAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tbilisi, Georgia
RELOCATE IS AVAILABLE

**Phone**: +995 599 00 73 27 **Email**: set.adoyan@gmail.com

Telegram: defk1lla

**Github**: github.com/defk1lla **LinkedIn**: linkedin.com/in/defk1lla

# **SUMMARY**

My work experience has recently passed three years, but I continue to learn in order to introduce something new, useful and unique into the projects I work on. I am self-supporting, have good self education skills, and love to solve complex and interesting tasks.

# **EDUCATION**

Georgian Technical University, Tbilisi

BACHELOR'S DEGREE SEPTEMBER 2018 – JUNE 2022

Faculty: Informatics and control systems

**Speciality**: Informatics

### **PROJECTS**

- defk1lla.vercel.app
- github.com/defk1lla

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Synmetrix (Open Source)

FRONTEND DEVELOPER AUGUST 2023 - PRENEST

Rewrote an old client to new technologies. Stack: React/Zustand/Vite/Vitest/TypeScript.

# **Space Dog**

LEAD FRONTEND DEVELOPER AUGUST 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Managed the development team for a project to search for air tickets. I did code reviews, compiled tasks, and built the project architecture. I have migrated a project from NextJS12 to NextJS14.

#### Freelance

HTML CODER/FRONTEND DEVELOPER NOVEMBER 2020 - AUGUST 2022

# **SKILLS**

- Frontend: TypeScript/JavaScript, ReactJS/NextJS, Redux/RTK, Mobx, Zustand, GraphQL, JQuery
- Backend: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, HTTP/REST
- HTML/CSS: HTML, CSS, BEM, Bootstrap, MUI, Styled Components
- Preprocessors: SASS/SCSS, LESS, Sylus
- Instruments: npm, yarn, Gulp, Webpack, Vite, Git/Github
- Testing: Vitest, Jest, react-testing-library
- Languages: Armenian (Native), Russian (Native), Georgian (Pre-intermediate), English (Beginner)

